

<u>Omar aboghadeer</u>

Senior Frontend Developer

omar.abo.ghadeer@hotmail.com

(+2 011-136-9578

My Contact

Ain Shames, Cairo, Egypt

aboghadeer.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/omar -abo-ghadeer-4925a6b1/

Hard Skill

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML & CSS
- Angular 2+
- Ionic 2+
- React
- GIT

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

New Cairo Academy
Bachelor of Computer Science
Completed in 2016

Extra Activities

Owner | House Co-working space Apr., 2018 – Jun., 2020

- Provide private spaces equipped to work
- Helping Students by providing courses for them with good price and rooms for their projects

About Me

Senior Web Developer specializing n front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Wellversed in numerous programming languages and frameworks including JavaScript, Dart, HTML5, CSS, Flutter, Angular 2+, Ionic 2+. And Strong background in Websites, Mobile Apps, and CRM & ERP systems

Professional Experience

Senior Frontend Developer | e-finance Dec, 2021 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Integration with others' internal systems.
- · Acts as a tech lead inside my team.
- · Assign and review tasks.

Senior Frontend Developer | Etisalat Misr Jan, 2021 – Nov, 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible for the revamps of the Etisalat website and shop portal.
- Integration with others' internal systems.
- Acted as a tech lead inside my team.
- Assign and review tasks.
- Gave them sessions about JavaScript frameworks and the differences between them.

Frontend Developer | Fabrica Creative Studio *May, 2018 – Dec, 2020*

Key responsibilities:

- Design and build advanced Mobile Apps using Iconic 2+, Websites, and Dashboard Systems using Angular 2+.
- Collaborate with other teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Work with outside data sources and APIs
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance.

UI Developer | EasyKash Oct, 2017 – Apr, 2018

Key responsibilities:

 Responsible for modification and maintenance of EasyKash app and web application user interface, working closely with our server-side developer team to ensure we deliver the full experience to our users, I also design mobile-based features using a cross-application platform